A Guide to the Commonwealth Fund records, Advanced Medical Fellowships, SG 1, Series 3 FA275
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Fellowships and Awards in the Health Field, 1933-1978; 2
  - Flink, Edmund B., November 12, 1947-October 15, 1952 (Box 13, Folder 164)
  - Flitter, Hessel H., February 28, 1956-October 10, 1957 (Box 14, Folder 165)
  - Fortier, Claude, January 27, 1954-July 24, 1957 (Box 14, Folder 166)
  - Freedman, David A., July 14, 1949-October 8, 1951 (Box 14, Folder 167)
  - Freymann, Moye W., December 6, 1951-July 10, 1962 (Box 14, Folder 168)
  - Friedberg, Felix, June 1, 1961-October 15, 1964 (Box 14, Folder 169)
  - Fruton, Joseph S., October 30, 1961-May 27, 1963 (Box 14, Folder 170)
  - Frye, William W., October 24, 1938-January 23, 1941 (Box 14, Folder 171)
  - Fuhrman, Frederick A., May 4, 1964-August 28, 1967 (Box 14, Folder 172)
  - Fulmer, Hugh Scott, May 27, 1960-October 19, 1961 (Box 14, Folder 173)
  - Furchgott, Robert F., July 21, 1961-October 18, 1963 (Box 14, Folder 174)
  - Galdston, Iago, July 14, 1961-August 2, 1966 (Box 14, Folder 175)
  - Gambrell, Winton Elizabeth, October 13, 1939-June 25, 1942 (Box 14, Folder 176)
  - Gambrell, Winton Elizabeth, May 5, 1944-September 19, 1948 (Box 15, Folder 177)
  - Gammon, George D., November 6, 1937-December 21, 1939 (Box 15, Folder 178)
  - Gaskiill, Herbert S., October 18, 1945-November 1, 1956 (Box 15, Folder 179)
  - Gee, Helen H., March 15, 1960-September 30, 1962 (Box 15, Folder 180)
  - Gellhorn, Alfred, September 18, 1962-January 28, 1970 (Box 15, Folder 181)
  - Gellis, Sydney S., October 27, 1958-January 6, 1960 (Box 15, Folder 182)
  - Gemmill, Chalmers L., September 15, 1964-October 10, 1966 (Box 15, Folder 183)
  - Gendel, Benjamin R., March 28, 1966-May 29, 1969 (Box 15, Folder 184)
  - Genest, Jacques, December 27, 1945 to January 24, 1957; August 30, 1965 to September 14, 1965 (Box 15, Folder 185)
  - Gersh, Isidore, November 29, 1949-August 17, 1954 (Box 15, Folder 186)
  - Giansiracusa, Joseph E., September 4, 1945-December 6, 1950 (Box 15, Folder 187)
  - Giarman, Nicholas J., September 14, 1966-December 10, 1968 (Box 15, Folder 188)
  - Gil, Javier Robles, April 29, 1942-February 16, 1948 (Box 16, Folder 189)
  - Gilder, Helena, March 5, 1942-July 19, 1945 (Box 16, Folder 190)
  - Gilmer, Robert Lee, October 14, 1952-July 25, 1955 (Box 16, Folder 191)
  - Ginsberg, Harold S., September 15, 1965-June 27, 1966 (Box 16, Folder 192)
  - Ginsberg, Jack M., March 11, 1964-November 23, 1976 (Box 16, Folder 193)
  - Gjessing, Erland C., November 3, 1964-October 2, 1967 (Box 16, Folder 194)
  - Glaser, Gilbert H., March 16, 1964-September 30, 1966 (Box 16, Folder 195)
  - Glick, David, August 10, 1948 to September 6, 1949; November 18, 1957 to December 11, 1963 (Box 16, Folder 196)
  - Golden, Abner, October 20, 1947-June 6, 1957 (Box 16, Folder 197)
  - Goldwasser, Eugene, July 12, 1965-April 7, 1966 (Box 16, Folder 198)
  - Goodhart, Gordon E., February 14, 1957-July 6, 1959 (Box 16, Folder 199)
  - Goodrich, Charles H., January 17, 1956-March 2, 1961 (Box 16, Folder 200)
  - Gordan, Gilbert S., November 21, 1946 to August 5, 1948; July 13, 1962 to April 15, 1966 (Box 16, Folder 201)
  - Gots, Joseph S., June 19, 1964-January 9, 1967 (Box 17, Folder 202)
  - Grant, Robert P., December 2, 1960-November 15, 1965 (Box 17, Folder 203)
  - Grant, Wallace W., December 22, 1950-June 24, 1955 (Box 17, Folder 204)
  - Green, Harold D., September 9, 1938-March 1, 1941 (Box 17, Folder 205)
  - Green, Robert Holt, June 29, 1960-January 23, 1962 (Box 17, Folder 206)
  - Greenberg, Nahman, August 27, 1956-October 31, 1958 (Box 17, Folder 207)
  - Greene, William A., Jr., May 14, 1947-December 8, 1955 (Box 17, Folder 208)
  - Greenspan, Richard H., May 13, 1964-January 6, 1966 (Box 17, Folder 209)
  - Greep, Roy O., October 23, 1958-August 28, 1963 (Box 17, Folder 210)
  - Gregory, Ian, June 9, 1957-January 14, 1965 (Box 17, Folder 211)
  - Grigsby, Margaret Elizabeth, March 14, 1962-November 30, 1964 (Box 17, Folder 212)
  - Gross, Ruth T., October 28, 1958-February 5, 1963 (Box 17, Folder 213)
  - Grossman, Lawrence, February 10, 1963-November 16, 1964 (Box 17, Folder 214)
  - Guilbert. Paul W., April 22, 1953-January 24, 1957 (Box 17, Folder 215)
  - Gunstad, Borghild S., November 26, 1938-September 29, 1939 (Box 18, Folder 216)
  - Gurney, Ronald W., July 28, 1941-April 8, 1949 (Box 18, Folder 217)
  - Haggerty, Robert J., September 13, 1960-January 11, 1963 (Box 18, Folder 218)
  - Ham, George C., July 21, 1939 to January 25, 1943; June 6, 1961 to December 9, 1963 (Box 18, Folder 219)
  - Ham, Thomas Hale, May 9, 1957-November 4, 1963 (Box 18, Folder 220)
  - Hamlin, Robert H., July 26, 1950-July 2, 1959 (Box 18, Folder 221)
  - Hamolsky, Milton W., January 16, 1961-September 6, 1962 (Box 18, Folder 222)
  - Harmel, Merel Hibler, January 16, 1961-February 3, 1964 (Box 18, Folder 223)
  - Harris, Harold J., March 16, 1965-March 28, 1967 (Box 18, Folder 224)
  - Harrison, Saul I., March 11, 1965-December 19, 1966 (Box 18, Folder 225)
  - Hartung, Walter, September 8, 1939-September 20, 1941 (Box 18, Folder 226)
  - Hasselbacher, Ona M., May 26, 1954-November 10, 1958 (Box 18, Folder 227)
  - Haugaard, Niels, October 14, 1964-September 19, 1956 (Box 19, Folder 228)
  - Hawkins, David R., December 9, 1949 to December 8, 1955; September 10, 1962 to August 21, 1974 (Box 19, Folder 229)
  - Heald, Felix P., November 18, 1965-July 7, 1966 (Box 19, Folder 230)
  - Hechter, Oscar, May 31, 1963-January 18, 1966 (Box 19, Folder 231)
  - Heggeness, Franklin W., March 19, 1962-December 6, 1963 (Box 19, Folder 232)
  - Heinecke, Christoph M., January 30, 1953-July 13, 1961 (Box 19, Folder 233)
  - Heistad, Gordon T., March 6, 1963-October 30, 1967 (Box 19, Folder 234)
  - Hempelmann, Louis H., Jr., October 29, 1940-October 15, 1947 (Box 19, Folder 235)
  - Hendrickson, Willard J., May 17, 1966-February 10, 1970 (Box 19, Folder 236)
  - Henriksen, Sverre Dick, April 29, 1940-January 14, 1946 (Box 19, Folder 237)
  - Henry Phipps Psychiatric Clinic [Johns Hopkins University], March 31, 1949-September 6, 1951 (Box 19, Folder 238)
  - Hiatt, Howard H., October 14, 1959 to November 25, 1963; February 28, 1968 to March 26, 1970 (Box 19, Folder 239)
  - Hinckley, Robert G., November 29, 1937-February 17, 1945 (Box 20, Folder 240)
  - Hoberman, Henry D., September 30, 1958 to September 15, 1960; January 9, 1964 to January 24, 1966; April 27, 1966 to July 19, 1973 (Box 20, Folder 241)
  - Hogness, David S., April 1, 1968-July 23, 1968 (Box 20, Folder 242)
  - Hollingshead, August B., June 10, 1957-October 3, 1958 (Box 20, Folder 243)
  - Holt, Joseph P., December 21, 1938-October 26, 1942 (Box 20, Folder 244)
  - Horecker, Bernard L., April 18, 1966-February 15, 1967 (Box 20, Folder 245)
  - Horowitz, Milton J., November 16, 1960-September 19, 1962 (Box 20, Folder 246)
  - Horstmann, Dorothy, November 1, 1941-September 7, 1943 (Box 20, Folder 247)
  - Hsia, David Yi-Yung, June 27, 1960-May 15, 1967 (Box 20, Folder 249)
  - Huang, Kee C., March 8, 1966-July 15, 1968 (Box 20, Folder 250)
  - Huddleston, O. Leonard, November 10, 1937-August 30, 1941 (Box 20, Folder 251)
    - Howe, Calderon, January 11, 1961-October 1, 1962 (Box 20, Folder 248)
  - Hudson, Robert P., April 30, 1963-June 5, 1964 (Box 20, Folder 252)
  - Hume, Michael, June 30, 1965-May 16, 1966 (Box 20, Folder 253)
  - Hungerford, Gerald G., February 23, 1965-October 6, 1966 (Box 21, Folder 254)
  - Hunt, Joseph McVicker, June 10, 1959-November 30, 1961 (Box 21, Folder 255)
  - Hurst, J. Willis, April 27, 1960-March 11, 1963 (Box 21, Folder 256)
  - Imagawa, David T., March 21, 1962-May 29, 1969 (Box 21, Folder 257)
  - Ingram, Walter Rex, October 4, 1957-January 26, 1960 (Box 21, Folder 258)
  - Jacobson, Harold G., August 17, 1965-May 21, 1974 (Box 21, Folder 259)
  - Jandorf, Bernard J., May 6, 1942-June 28, 1944 (Box 21, Folder 260)
  - Jensen, Gordon D., September 29, 1950-August 31, 1953 (Box 21, Folder 261)
  - Jensen, Wallace N., September 4, 1962-June 7, 1963 (Box 21, Folder 262)
  - Johnson, J. Garth, April 23, 1958-May 9, 1962 (Box 21, Folder 263)
  - Judge, Richard D., June 2, 1965-April 21, 1967 (Box 21, Folder 264)
  - Kaplan, Henry S., January 16, 1954-June 25, 1965 (Box 21, Folder 265)
  - Kaplan, Nathan O., December 10, 1959-March 11, 1963 (Box 21, Folder 266)
  - Kappas, Attaliah, September 9, 1960-September 1, 1965 (Box 22, Folder 267)
  - Karlson, Karl E., October 2, 1964-November 14, 1966 (Box 22, Folder 268)
  - Karush, Fred, June 4, 1965-March 28, 1966 (Box 22, Folder 269)
  - Kaufman, I. Charles, January 20, 1958-June 22, 1961 (Box 22, Folder 270)
  - Keats, Theodore E., May 1, 1962-November 22, 1965 (Box 22, Folder 271)
  - Kempe, C. Henry, June 25, 1968-February 19, 1969 (Box 22, Folder 272)
  - Kenward, John F., February 13, 1950-June 29, 1961 (Box 22, Folder 273)
  - Kern, Fred, Jr., March 1, 1961-January 31, 1966 (Box 22, Folder 274)
  - Kiesewetter, William B., October 16, 1963-September 27, 1965 (Box 22, Folder 275)
  - King, Carol L., March 15, 1968-November 29, 1973 (Box 22, Folder 276)
  - Kirchner, John A., November 27, 1961-March 14, 1966 (Box 22, Folder 277)
  - Kitay, Julian I., September 28, 1955 to February 10, 1957; March 29, 1967 to September 20, 1967 (Box 23, Folder 278)
  - Klatskin, Gerald, September 5, 1963-September 10, 1964 (Box 23, Folder 279)
  - Knowlton, G. Clinton, September 22, 1939-September 10, 1941 (Box 23, Folder 280)
  - Kohl, Schuyler G., January 25, 1952-September 23, 1954 (Box 23, Folder 281)
  - Kolb, Lawrence C., April 3, 1964-August 21, 1969 (Box 23, Folder 282)
  - Kozloff, Lloyd M., August 14, 1953-December 2, 1957 (Box 23, Folder 283)
  - Krampitz, Lester O., October 21, 1963-December 18, 1963 (Box 23, Folder 284)
  - Kretchmer, Norman, October 9, 1951 to September 8, 1953; February 6, 1957 to December 24, 1958; January 22, 1964 to August 12, 1966 (Box 23, Folder 285)
  - Kriss, Joseph P., September 6, 1956-February 20, 1958 (Box 23, Folder 286)
  - Kruse, Cornelius W., June 18, 1957-February 10, 1959 (Box 23, Folder 287)
  - Kugel, Robert B., August 15, 1949-May 12, 1955 (Box 24, Folder 288)
  - Labate, John S., December 3, 1938-October 21, 1941 (Box 24, Folder 289)
  - Labby, Daniel H., May 8, 1958-March 5, 1969 (Box 24, Folder 290)
  - Lacey, John I., September 19, 1956-June 22, 1959 (Box 24, Folder 291)
  - Lamden, Merton P., January 9, 1961-December 10, 1962 (Box 24, Folder 292)
  - Landau, Bernard Robert, November 19, 1964-July 5, 1966 (Box 24, Folder 293)
  - Landau, Richard L., May 16, 1963-September 22, 1971 (Box 24, Folder 294)
  - Landau, William M., December 10, 1951-April 24, 1952 (Box 24, Folder 295)
  - Landor, John H., February 23, 1965-April 17, 1967 (Box 24, Folder 296)
  - Larner, Joseph, August 22, 1962-September 13, 1965 (Box 24, Folder 297)
  - Latta, Harrison, March 9, 1959-February 20, 1962 (Box 24, Folder 298)
  - Lawrence, H. Sherwood, January 6, 1959-February 28, 1963 (Box 24, Folder 299)
  - Lazarsfeld, Paul F., April 7, 1961-February 6, 1963 (Box 24, Folder 300)
  - Leavell, Hugh R., October 18, 1937-February 14, 1941 (Box 25, Folder 301)
  - LeCompte, Philip M., November 19, 1938-September 22, 1941 (Box 25, Folder 302)
  - Lee, Kwang Soo, October 2, 1962-June 15, 1967 (Box 25, Folder 303)
  - Leigh, Ted F., November 16, 1965-October 17, 1966 (Box 25, Folder 304)
  - Lembcke, Paul A., March 19, 1956-June 29, 1959 (Box 25, Folder 305)
  - Lerner, Aaron B., June 14, 1960-May 4, 1964 (Box 25, Folder 306)
  - Levine, Isidore, December 8, 1955-February 10, 1959 (Box 25, Folder 307)
  - Levine, Myron, May 12, 1965-June 6, 1966 (Box 25, Folder 308)
  - Lewis, George T., November 28, 1938-June 26, 1941 (Box 25, Folder 309)
  - Lezer, Leon R., June 5, 1959-June 12, 1963 (Box 25, Folder 310)
  - Libet, Benjamin, October 17, 1955 to January 26, 1959; February 19, 1963 to June 7, 1968 (Box 25, Folder 311)
  - Lichtman, Herbert C., April 16, 1959-June 12, 1962 (Box 26, Folder 312)
  - Lidz, Theodore, October 31, 1956-August 9, 1965 (Box 26, Folder 313)
  - Lief, Harold T., September 5, 1962-November 29, 1965 (Box 26, Folder 314)
  - Lindzey, Gardner, March 5, 1952-March 1, 1956 (Box 26, Folder 315)
  - Lippard, Vernon W., August 24, 1959-August 22, 1960 (Box 26, Folder 316)
  - Loeb, Robert F., December 17, 1964-February 17, 1965 (Box 26, Folder 317)
  - Loewenstein, Rudolph M., October 29, 1963-January 20, 1966 (Box 26, Folder 318)
  - Loewenstein, Werner R., April 25, 1966-September 26, 1967 (Box 26, Folder 319)
  - Logan, Myrtle, March 25, 1946-December 20, 1949 (Box 26, Folder 320)
  - London, Irving M., October 9, 1961-October 4, 1963 (Box 26, Folder 321)
  - Long, Cyril Norman H., September 25, 1963-January 13, 1965 (Box 26, Folder 322)
  - Longwell, Bernard B., November 23, 1937-September 10, 1957 (Box 26, Folder 323)
  - Loomis, T. A., November 18, 1960-January 31, 1962 (Box 26, Folder 324)
  - Lord, Mason F., August 1, 1960-November 18, 1965 (Box 26, Folder 325)
  - Lord, Mason F., August 1, 1960-November 18, 1965 (Box 26, Folder 326)
  - Lotspeich, William D., February 16, 1962-May 17, 1965 (Box 27, Folder 327)
  - Lowrie, Robert J., October 15, 1957-October 11, 1961 (Box 27, Folder 328)
  - Lowry, Oliver H., November 17, 1938-December 23, 1940 (Box 27, Folder 329)
  - Lowy, Betram A., June 24, 1964-October 21, 1966 (Box 27, Folder 330)
  - Lubin, Martin, July 13, 1965-June 22, 1967 (Box 27, Folder 331)
  - Luckey, Thomas Donnell, March 18, 1960-April 3, 1963 (Box 27, Folder 332)
  - Lurie, Max B., August 6, 1959-July 20, 1965 (Box 27, Folder 333)
  - Lustman, Seymour L., December 8, 1953-December 21, 1965 (Box 27, Folder 334)
  - Lustman, Seymour L., December 8, 1953-December 21, 1965 (Box 27, Folder 335)
  - Luykx, Henrik M. C., May 14, 1942-January 28, 1948 (Box 27, Folder 336)
  - Lyons, Veronica, April 3, 1956-June 28, 1956 (Box 27, Folder 337)
  - Machella, Thomas E., November 6, 1937-October 14, 1941 (Box 27, Folder 338)
  - MacKrell, Thomas Nickols, April 27, 1965-May 31, 1966 (Box 27, Folder 339)
  - MacLean, Basil Clarendon, July 15, 1941-January 21, 1943 (Box 27, Folder 340)
  - Madden, Sidney C., December 17, 1965-November 30, 1966 (Box 28, Folder 341)
  - Maeir, David M., November 4, 1963-February 28, 1964 (Box 28, Folder 342)
  - Mako, Aladar Edgar, January 24, 1940-November 6, 1941 (Box 28, Folder 343)
  - Mandel, H. George, July 31, 1955 to September 8, 1958; October 7, 1963 to May 21, 1965 (Box 28, Folder 344)
  - Mann, Edward C., Novemer 12, 1953-March 29, 1957 (Box 28, Folder 345)
  - Mansour, Tag Eldin, October 23, 1964-September 9, 1966 (Box 28, Folder 346)
  - Margolis, Philip M., August 28, 1963-December 28, 1966 (Box 28, Folder 347)
  - Marinetti, Guido V., April 21, 1964-January 9, 1967 (Box 28, Folder 348)
  - Markee, Joseph E., April 27, 1965-December 11, 1967 (Box 28, Folder 349)
  - Markham, Charles H., October 14, 1963-October 14, 1965 (Box 28, Folder 350)
  - Marks, Paul A., September 13, 1960-March 21, 1963 (Box 28, Folder 351)
  - Marra, Edward F., Deember 1, 1953-March 31, 1955 (Box 28, Folder 352)
  - Martel, William, April 29, 1966-April 2, 1968 (Box 29, Folder 353)
  - Martin, Samuel P., October 30, 1968-June 10, 1969 (Box 29, Folder 354)
  - Martt, Jack M., November 29, 1965-May 31, 1967 (Box 29, Folder 355)
  - Marvin, Horace N., October 24, 1962 to March 31, 1964; February 3, 1965 to July 1, 1965; April 24, 1972 to May 2, 1972 (Box 29, Folder 356)
  - Masters, Richard, January 11, 1963-December 23, 1965 (Box 29, Folder 357)
  - Masuoka, David T., February 26, 1964-December 20, 1965 (Box 29, Folder 358)
  - May, Charles D., September 4, 1940-January 30, 1942 (Box 29, Folder 359)
  - McKerracher, D. G., November 28, 1951-August 5, 1953 (Box 29, Folder 360)
  - McLennan, Charles E., October 24, 1939 to June 18, 1942; November 18, 1964 to August 16, 1965 (Box 29, Folder 361)
  - McManus, Joseph F. A., March 10, 1959-April 23, 1962 (Box 29, Folder 362)
  - Mehl, John W., July 14, 1958-December 29, 1959 (Box 29, Folder 363)
  - Melechen, Norman E., November 12, 1965-April 26, 1966 (Box 29, Folder 364)
  - Melzack, Ronald, July 5, 1953-April 21, 1961 (Box 30, Folder 365)
  - Merlis, Jerome K., January 8, 1940-September 22, 1941 (Box 30, Folder 366)
  - Miller, C. Arden, April 8, 1965-February 17, 1967 (Box 30, Folder 367)
  - Miller, George E., April 17, 1968-August 23, 1968 (Box 30, Folder 368)
  - Miller, Herbert C., January 20, 1966-January 22, 1968 (Box 30, Folder 369)
  - Miller, Theodore R., July 27, 1962-December 30, 1966 (Box 30, Folder 370)
  - Milstone, Jacob Haskell, February 14, 1940 to February 17, 1950; April 3, 1961 to October 2, 1967 (Box 30, Folder 371)
  - Milstone, Jacob Haskell, February 14, 1940 to February 17, 1950; April 3, 1961 to October 2, 1967 (Box 30, Folder 372)
  - Mirsky, I. Arthur, September 25, 1957 to January 7, 1958; September 17, 1959 to May 12, 1964 (Box 30, Folder 373)
  - Mohn, James F., May 14, 1963-June 1, 1964 (Box 30, Folder 374)
  - Mommaerts, Wilfried, January 17, 1962-September 10, 1964 (Box 31, Folder 375)
  - Monroe, Russell R., December 3, 1963-November 1, 1967 (Box 31, Folder 376)
  - Moore, James C., October 18, 1948-February 16, 1951 (Box 31, Folder 377)
  - Moore, John W., October 26, 1965 to April 9, 1969; June 3-4, 1976 (Box 31, Folder 378)
  - Moore, John W. - Physiological Instrumentation, March 27, 1969 (Box 31, Folder 379)
  - Moore, John W. - Physiological Instrumentation, March 27, 1969 (Box 31, Folder 380)
  - Morgan, Herbert R., December 31, 1965-September 13, 1968 (Box 31, Folder 381)
  - Moritz, Alan Richards, June 27, 1957-March 13, 1958 (Box 31, Folder 382)
  - Most, Harry, May 16, 1941-January 9, 1950 (Box 31, Folder 383)
  - Motulsky, Arno G., April 19, 1966-April 19, 1968 (Box 31, Folder 384)
  - Mulholland, John H., October 9, 1939-October 16, 1941 (Box 32, Folder 385)
  - Munter, Preston K., April 2, 1952-December 10, 1962 (Box 32, Folder 386)
  - Muntwyler, Edward, October 26, 1959-September 20, 1960 (Box 32, Folder 387)
  - Murray, Margaret R., March 6, 1963-January 18, 1965 (Box 32, Folder 388)
  - Mushatt, Cecil, March 21, 1947-May 19, 1959 (Box 32, Folder 389)
  - Nelson, Leonard, February 26, 1963-October 4, 1967 (Box 32, Folder 390)
  - Newell, Kenneth W., April 26, 1966-December 22, 1966 (Box 32, Folder 391)
  - Newman, W. R. Elton, May 11, 1954-May 21, 1957 (Box 32, Folder 392)
  - Newton, Thomas H., April 28, 1964-April 3, 1968 (Box 32, Folder 393)
  - Ngai, Shih-hsun, November 12, 1963-October 30, 1967 (Box 33, Folder 394)
  - Norbury, Frank B., December 9, 1949-December 8, 1955 (Box 33, Folder 395)
  - Novelli, G. David, March 29, 1946-September 21, 1948 (Box 33, Folder 396)
  - Noyes, Robert W., July 14, 1960-December 14, 1971 (Box 33, Folder 397)
  - Odell, Gerard B., June 2, 1952-December 30, 1959 (Box 33, Folder 398)
  - Olason, Fridgeir, July 20, 1940-January 8, 1945 (Box 33, Folder 399)
  - Orfirer, Alexander, December 16, 1948-March 31, 1950 (Box 33, Folder 400)
  - Osler, Abraham, April 10, 1963-February 9, 1966 (Box 33, Folder 401)
  - Ovary, Zoltan, August 5, 1966-September 27, 1966 (Box 33, Folder 402)
  - Page, Robert G., July 31, 1962-June 9, 1966 (Box 33, Folder 403)
  - Palubinskas, Alphonse J., July 29, 1966-March 19, 1968 (Box 33, Folder 404)
  - Pappenheimer, A. M., Jr., May 22, 1950-July 17, 1952 (Box 33, Folder 405)
  - Parker, Beulah, November 25, 1950-April 27, 1955 (Box 33, Folder 406)
  - Parker, Francis P., October 18, 1939-January 21, 1943 (Box 33, Folder 407)
  - Parks, John, May 7, 1963-April 1, 1965 (Box 34, Folder 408)
  - Parmalee, Arthur H., Jr., May 29, 1958-June 16, 1966 (Box 34, Folder 409)
  - Patek, Paul R., May 14, 1963-April 9, 1965 (Box 34, Folder 410)
  - Paul, Benjamin D., November 2, 1949-May 24, 1957 (Box 34, Folder 411)
  - Pavenstedt, Eleanor, December 3, 1962-June 11, 1964 (Box 34, Folder 412)
  - Peanasky, Robert J., November 15, 1965-March 10, 1967 (Box 34, Folder 413)
  - Perlmann, Gertrude E., February 5, 1945 to November 9, 1954; October 29, 1968 to November 4, 1968 (Box 34, Folder 414)
  - Peters, Theodore, Jr., August 13, 1957-April 27, 1959 (Box 34, Folder 415)
  - Piatte, Jean, May 19, 1948-September 20, 1949 (Box 34, Folder 416)
  - Pine, Harold B., July 18, 1955-November 29, 1957 (Box 34, Folder 417)
  - Pirofsky, Bernard, November 24, 1964-October 25, 1967 (Box 34, Folder 418)
  - Platou, Ralph V., November 2, 1960-February 9, 1965 (Box 34, Folder 419)
  - Pollock, George H., August 19, 1949 to December 18, 1953; January 21, 1957 to December 2, 1964; December 4-12, 1969 (Box 35, Folder 420)
  - Ponseti, I. V., December 9, 1964-October 27, 1966 (Box 35, Folder 421)
  - Porter, Robert W., October 9, 1953-April 13, 1954 (Box 35, Folder 422)
  - Prather, Perry F., April 17, 1957-October 31, 1960 (Box 35, Folder 423)
  - Read, Charles Herbert, January 19, 1949-May 9, 1958 (Box 35, Folder 424)
  - Recant, Lillian, February 21, 1947-January 26, 1953 (Box 35, Folder 425)
  - Register, U. D., September 14, 1962-January 11, 1965 (Box 35, Folder 426)
  - Reichlin, Seymour, December 5, 1951-January 13, 1961 (Box 35, Folder 427)
  - Reichsman, Franz K., July 2, 1951-April 6, 1959 (Box 35, Folder 428)
  - Reiser, Morton F., May 19, 1950-January 25, 1955 (Box 35, Folder 429)
  - Reynolds, Samuel R. M., December 28, 1964-April 18, 1966 (Box 35, Folder 430)
  - Richards, Dickinson W., January 30, 1961-September 16, 1965 (Box 36, Folder 431)
  - Richards, Victor, September 8, 1949-October 11, 1951 (Box 36, Folder 432)
  - Richfield, Jerome, November 27, 1950 to February 26, 1951; November 10, 1954 to March 4, 1957 (Box 36, Folder 433)
  - Richmond, Jonas E., May 20, 1954-November 18, 1957 (Box 36, Folder 434)
  - Richmond, Julius B., February 27, 1961-May 13, 1963 (Box 36, Folder 435)
  - Richter, Curt P., June 5, 1964-October 24, 1967 (Box 36, Folder 436)
  - Roberg, Norman B., November 14, 1962-June 16, 1965 (Box 36, Folder 437)
  - Roberts, Frank L., December 30, 1942-September 13, 1943 (Box 36, Folder 438)
  - Robinson, J. M., March 31, 1954-July 29, 1955 (Box 36, Folder 439)
  - Rogatz, Peter, July 29, 1953-March 13, 1959 (Box 36, Folder 440)
  - Romano, John, April 24, 1958 to January 18, 1963; September 7, 1966 to September 22, 1966 (Box 36, Folder 441)
  - Romano, John, April 24, 1958 to January 18, 1963; September 7, 1966 to September 22, 1966 (Box 36, Folder 442)
  - Rose, Augustus Steele, December 1, 1961-January 12, 1965 (Box 37, Folder 443)
  - Rose, Noel R., January 20, 1958 to May 1, 1959; June 23, 1965 to February 14, 1968 (Box 37, Folder 444)
  - Rosenbaum, Milton, August 10, 1965-April 4, 1967 (Box 37, Folder 445)
  - Ross, Roderick C., September 20, 1948-November 14, 1950 (Box 37, Folder 446)
  - Rothman, Stephen, October 26, 1939-September 21, 1941 (Box 37, Folder 447)
  - Rudomanski, Victor, November 17, 1938-May 11, 1942 (Box 37, Folder 448)
  - Ruhe, David S., November 15, 1960-February 27, 1964 (Box 37, Folder 449)
  - Runyan, John W., December 28, 1949-August 28, 1951 (Box 37, Folder 450)
  - Samson, Donald C., February 17, 1948-December 8, 1955 (Box 37, Folder 451)
  - Samuels, Leo T., September 21, 1957-January 11, 1960 (Box 37, Folder 452)
  - Saslow, George, June 14, 1965-September 29, 1966 (Box 37, Folder 453)
  - Sattler, Dwight C., December 19, 1940-May 3, 1943 (Box 37, Folder 454)
  - Sawyer, Charles H., November 27, 1957 to February 8, 1960; June 8, 1964 to January 2, 1969 (Box 38, Folder 455)
  - Sawyer, Charles H., November 27, 1957 to February 8, 1960; June 8, 1964 to January 2, 1969 (Box 38, Folder 456)
  - Sawyer, Wilbur H., May 26, 1964-September 22, 1965 (Box 38, Folder 457)
  - Sayers, George, September 20, 1965-December 22, 1969 (Box 38, Folder 458)
  - Scharrer, Ernst A., September 14, 1960-May 25, 1965 (Box 38, Folder 459)